mateofmine.com 2013-06-05

# Mate of Mine | Local Business Directory Powered by Facebook

Welcome to Mate of Mine Facebook Business Directory Privacy Policy. 

[Mate of Mine Local Business Directory Powered by Facebook.](http://www.mateofmine.com/) Your privacy is very important to us. You must read and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy before becoming a Mate of Mine account holder. As part of the normal operation of our services we collect, use and, in some cases, disclose information about you to third parties. This Privacy Policy governs the information we collect about you and your use of information we provide to you. By accepting this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Mate of Mine User Agreement. 

Although this policy may seem long, we have prepared a detailed policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make an informed decision. The privacy practices of this notice apply to the website located at http://www.mateofmine.com (collectively the "Site"). Mate of Mine is subject to the requirements of applicable law and, in the case of Australia, the requirements of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), (as amended by the private sector provisions which came into effect on 21 December 2001) (the "Privacy Act") 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Mate of Mine by sending email to admin@mateofmine.com Also, you may wish to refer to the Office of the Federal Privacy Commissioner which may be contacted at the following site: http://www.privacy.gov.au for more information on the Privacy Act. 

This Privacy Policy contains a number of references to other information pages on our Site and other websites. Please note: underlined words and phrases are click-through links to these pages and websites. Mate of Mine strongly recommends that as you read this Privacy Policy, you click on such links to obtain further important details about the Privacy Policy, as they may contain further terms and conditions which apply to you as a Mate of Mine Account holder. 

### Experience the web with Facebook friends.

Social plugins let you see what your friends have liked, commented on or shared on sites across the web. All social plugins are extensions of Facebook and are specifically designed so none of your data is shared with the sites on which they appear. 

### An Important Note About Children.

Children (persons under the age of 18 years) are not eligible to use our services unsupervised and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under the age of 18 years, you can use this service only in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians. 

### Information We Collect

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safer and customised experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customise our services to make your experience safer and easier. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for this purpose and to achieve this goal. 

To fully use our services, you will need to register using our online registration form, where you will be required to provide us with your contact information and other personal information. You are required to provide us with your full name. Under some circumstances we may require some additional necessary financial information, such as, but not limited to: if you are registering using an email account at a free email service, or posting a listing on our site. We use your financial information, including credit card information to verify your name, address, and other contact information. 

We automatically track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on our Site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand and serve you and our community. This information is compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address. 

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of our Site. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customised services. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". We also use "cookies" to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information which is targeted to your interests. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our Site. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our Site and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session. 

Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of our Site that are placed by third parties. For example, if you view a web page created by a user, there may be a "cookie" placed within that web page. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties. 

If you choose to submit a business listing on our Site, We collect other users' comments about you. 

If you choose to post messages in our site or other message areas or leave feedback for other users, we will collect and store such information that you disclose to us. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

### Our Use of Your Information

We use personal information about you (including but not limited to the information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site) to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, help ensure safe trading on our Site, and enforce our User Agreement. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your information to identify users using multiple Usernames or aliases. 

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyse site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and customise our Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve our Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safer and customised experience while using our services. 

You agree that we may use your information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy you expressly agree to receive this information. 

### Our Disclosure of Your Information 

Although Mate of Mine uses industry standard practices to protect your personal information, due to technical limitations, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances (further details of which are set out below in the "Legal Requests" section), or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we cannot and do not guarantee, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personal information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be disclosed, and by agreeing to the User Agreement and Privacy Policy you expressly agree that your personal information may be disclosed by Mate of Mine in the following ways: 

Partners. We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personal information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to partners and other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address, password, credit card number, and bank account number, are never disclosed to advertisers. 

Mate of Mine Community. Throughout the Site, you are identified by your Facebook name. As a result, other users and third parties might send you unsolicited email and be able to personally identify all of your activities on the Site. Even if your full name is not your email address, your full name can be used to identify you and your activities throughout the Site. 

External Service Providers. There are a number of services offered by external service providers that help you use our Site (e.g., co-branded sites, listing agents, authentication, mediation). If you choose to use these optional services, disclose personal information to the external service providers, and/or grant them permission to collect personal information about you, then their use of your personal information is governed by their privacy policy. We may, for your convenience, provide some of your personal information to the external service provider offering such services. However, before we disclose your personal information to an external service provider, you will have the opportunity to see what data is about to be sent and have the ability to approve the disclosure. To prevent our disclosure of your personal information to an external service provider, you can decline such disclosures or simply not use their services. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their services. 

Internal Service Providers. We may use internal service providers to facilitate our services (e.g., search, discussion boards, surveys) and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to them. In some instances, the internal service provider may collect information directly from you (such as the situation where we ask an internal service provider to conduct a survey for us). In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the internal service provider, and all information disclosures you make will be strictly optional. In all cases, the information we supply the internal service providers is restricted by confidentiality agreements. If you provide additional information to an internal service provider directly, then their use of your information is governed by their applicable privacy policy. 

Other Corporate Entities. We share much of our data, including personal information about you, with FundBreak companies & joint ventures that are committed to serving your online trading needs and related services, as allowed by applicable law. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other users. Our subsidiaries and joint ventures follow privacy practices no less protective of all users than our practices described in this Privacy Policy, to the extent allowed by applicable law. It is possible that Mate of Mine, subsidiaries, its joint ventures, or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that Mate of Mine would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide the service. You will receive notice of such event (to the extent it occurs) as provided in Section 11 ("Notice") we will require that the new combined entity follow the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy. 

Legal Requests. Mate of Mine may lawfully disclose your personal information for law enforcement or regulatory purposes. Mate of Mine cooperates with law enforcement inquires and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights. We can (and you authorise us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other governmental officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary, appropriate or as otherwise permitted under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, piracy or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. 

### Control of Your Password

You are responsible for all actions taken with your password, including fees. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your Mate of Mine password to any third parties. If you choose to share your password or your information with third parties to provide you additional services, you agree that you are responsible for all actions taken with your password and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. 

### Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information

Following registration, you can review and change the information you submitted during registration including: 

Your registration information such as: name, company, address, city, state, post code, country, primary phone number, secondary phone number, fax number and gender. 

Your password (if you have supplied such information).. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes. Once posted, you cannot change or remove any public postings made in our forums or other message areas or the feedback area. 

### Other Information Collectors 

Except as otherwise expressly discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are project creators or project supporters on our Site or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy customs and policies. Since Mate of Mine does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

### Security 

Your Information is stored on Mate of Mine servers currently located in the United States. We use industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. 

### Notice

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments and our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. All changes to this policy are effective after we provide you with at least thirty (30) days' notice of the changes by posting the changes on the announcements board and sending email to users who select such notification preference We provide you with thirty (30) days notice to allow you the opportunity to notify Mate of Mine if you do not agree to such changes as described in Section 8. 

If you have any questions, please contact admin@mateofmine.com
